<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wikipedia on Universal</title>
    <link>https://mcy0325.github.io/teamWebPage/authors/wikipedia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in wikipedia on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 21:29:20 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mcy0325.github.io/teamWebPage/authors/wikipedia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>https://mcy0325.github.io/teamWebPage/docker/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcy0325.github.io/teamWebPage/docker/history/</guid>
      <description>Docker Inc. was founded by Kamel Founadi, Solomon Hykes, and Sebastien Pahl during the Y Combinator Summer 2010 startup incubator group and launched in 2011. The startup was also one of the 12 startups in Founder&amp;rsquo;s Den first cohort. Hykes started the Docker project in France as an internal project within dotCloud, a platform-as-a-service company.
Docker debuted to the public in Santa Clara at PyCon in 2013. It was released as open-source in March 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>https://mcy0325.github.io/teamWebPage/docker/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcy0325.github.io/teamWebPage/docker/tools/</guid>
      <description>Docker Compose is a tool for defining and running multi-container Docker applications.It uses YAML files to configure the application&amp;rsquo;s services and performs the creation and start-up process of all the containers with a single command. The docker-compose CLI utility allows users to run commands on multiple containers at once, for example, building images, scaling containers, running containers that were stopped, and more. Commands related to image manipulation, or user-interactive options, are not relevant in Docker Compose because they address one container.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
